[
	{
		"question": "When does India celebrate Independence Day?",
		"options": [
			"A. 15th August",
			"B. 2nd October",
			"C. 26th January",
			"D. 4th July"
		],
		"answer": "A. 15th August"
	},
	{
		"question": "Nobel prize is awarded for which of the following disciplines?",
		"options": [
			"A. Literature, peace and economics",
			"B. Medicine or Physiology",
			"C. Chemistry and Physics",
			"D. All the above"
		],
		"answer": "D. All the above"
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the theme of Asia health conference 2019?",
		"options": [
			"A. Competitiveness of India Inc- India@60: Forging Ahead",
			"B. Competitiveness of India Inc- India@75: Forging Ahead",
			"C. Competitiveness of India Inc- India@80: Forging Ahead",
			"D. Competitiveness of India Inc- India@90: Forging Ahead"
		],
		"answer": "B. Competitiveness of India Inc- India@75: Forging Ahead"
	},
	{
		"question": "Which state has Introduced new kin technology?",
		"options": [
			"A. Assam",
			"B. Delhi",
			"C. Haryana",
			"D. Punjab"
		],
		"answer": "D. Punjab"
	},
	{
		"question": "Who has won pro Kabadi League this season?",
		"options": [
			"A. Dabang Delhi",
			"B. Bengal Warriors",
			"C. Puneri paltan",
			"D. U Mumba"
		],
		"answer": "B. Bengal Warriors"
	},
	{
		"question": "First private train in India run between which of the two cities?",
		"options": [
			"A. Delhi-Lucknow",
			"B. Delhi-Ahmedabad",
			"C. Both of the above route",
			"D. None of the above"
		],
		"answer": "A. Delhi-Lucknow"
	},
	{
		"question": "As per a latest report by Brand Finance 2019, which is the India's most valuable brand?",
		"options": [
			"A. Reliance",
			"B. Tata Group",
			"C. State Bank of India",
			"D. Flipkart"
		],
		"answer": "B. Tata Group"
	},
	{
		"question": "At the end of March 2019, what was the amount of India's external debt?",
		"options": [
			"A. US $ 540 billion",
			"B. US $ 543 billion",
			"C. US $ 547 billion",
			"D. US $ 541 billion"
		],
		"answer": "B. US $ 543 billion"
	},
	{
		"question": "'LIBRA' an alternative of existing cryptocurrency like bitcoin is being developed by?",
		"options": [
			"A. Facebook",
			"B. Google",
			"C. Microsoft",
			"D. None of the above"
		],
		"answer": "A. Facebook"
	},
	{
		"question": "In which year was Sports Authority of India established?",
		"options": [
			"A. 1952",
			"B. 1967",
			"C. 1993",
			"D. 1982"
		],
		"answer": "D. 1982"
	},
	{
		"question": "Headquater of International Olympic Committee is situated at?",
		"options": [
			"A. Athens",
			"B. Lausanne",
			"C. Dubai",
			"D. None of the above"
		],
		"answer": "B. Lausanne"
	},
	{
		"question": "'The Coalition Years' is the autobiography of?",
		"options": [
			"A. L.K Advani",
			"B. Pranab Mukherjee",
			"C. Atal Behari Vajpayee",
			"D. Sonia Gandhi"
		],
		"answer": "B. Pranab Mukherjee"
	},
	{
		"question": "Which Indian revolutionary leader is known as 'Bagha Jatin'?",
		"options": [
			"A. Jatindranath Mukherjee",
			"B. Jatindranath Bannerjee",
			"C. Jatindranath Das",
			"D. Jatindranath bose"
		],
		"answer": "A. Jatindranath Mukherjee"
	},
	{
		"question": "Entomology studies what?",
		"options": [
			"A. Behavior of human beings",
			"B. Insects",
			"C. The origin and history of technical and scientific terms",
			"D. The formation of rocks"
		],
		"answer": "B. Insects"
	},
	{
		"question": "Galileo was an astronomer who",
		"options": [
			"A. Developed the telescope",
			"B. Discovered four satellites of Jupiter",
			"C. discovered that the movement of pendulum produces a regular time measurement",
			"D. All the above"
		],
		"answer": "B. Discovered four satellites of Jupiter"
	},
	{
		"question": "Who is the father of geometry?",
		"options": [
			"A. Aristotle",
			"B. Euclid",
			"C. Pythagoras",
			"D. Kepler"
		],
		"answer": "B. Euclid"
	},
	{
		"question": "Indian player Jude Felix is popular for which sports?",
		"options": [
			"A. Volleyball",
			"B. Football",
			"C. Hockey",
			"D. Tennis"
		],
		"answer": "C. Hockey"
	},
	{
		"question": "Who is the current chief of the world bank group?",
		"options": [
			"A. Donald Tusk",
			"B. David Malpass",
			"C. Christine Lagarde",
			"D. Jim Yong Kim"
		],
		"answer": "B. David Malpass"
	}
]